netotrade.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy - NetoTrade

We are committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors and users of this website. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us. We will only use your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy. 

Our privacy policy statement will be reviewed from time to time to take into account any new laws or technological changes to our operations and practices and to ensure it remains appropriate to the changing environment.   
By using this website, you consent to us using your personal information as set out below.

## What personal information do we collect?

If you decide to apply to open an account with us, there is certain information that we will require from you in order to do so. This information includes but is not limited to personal details such as name, address, date of birth, contact details, employment details, assets and liabilities and other necessary financial information. 

From time to time we may also request further information to help us improve our service to you. We obtain most of the information directly from our customers through application or other forms, and from maintaining records provided during the course of ongoing customer service. We may also collect information about your use of the website, such as pages visited, frequency and duration, visit and trading activities. How do we use this information? We will use the information collected from you to provide the information and services requested by you and to improve the quality of our service. Unless you are informed otherwise, the personal information we hold is used for:

  * Establishing and managing your account;
  * Reviewing your ongoing needs;
  * Enhancing customer service and products;
  * Giving you ongoing information or opportunities that we believe may be relevant to you.

##   
Disclosure of Information

Depending on the product or service concerned and particular restrictions on sensitive information, this means that personal information may be disclosed to:

  * service providers and specialist advisers to us who have been contracted to provide us with administrative, financial, insurance, research or other services, 
  * introducing brokers with whom we have a mutual relationship (any of whom may be within or outside the European Economic Area), 
  * credit providers, courts, tribunals and regulatory authorities as agreed to or authorized by law, 
  * credit reporting or reference agencies, 
  * anyone authorized by an individual, as specified by that individual or the contract. 

If you do not want us to use your personal information please let us know in writing. If you decide to do so, we may not be able to continue to provide information, services and/or products requested by you.

### Updating your information

You may inform NetoTrade Global Investments LTD at any time that your personal details have changed or that you wish NetoTrade Global Investments LTD to delete personal information we hold about you by e-mailing us at[ support@netotrade.com](mailto:support@netotrade.com). NetoTrade Global Investments LTD will change or delete your personal information in accordance with your instructions, except to the extent that we are required to hold your personal information for regulatory or legal purposes so that we can provide you with the services you have requested and to maintain adequate business records.

### Use of Cookies

If you open an account with us, you will need to use our trading software, which enables us to use cookies in relation to your access to this website. Cookies are small files of information, which often include a unique identification number or value, which is stored on your computer’s hard drive as a result of you using this trading software and accessing this website. 

The purpose of this information is to provide you with a more relevant and effective experience on this website, including presenting web pages according to your needs or preferences. Cookies are frequently used on many websites on the internet and you can choose if and how a cookie will be accepted by changing your preferences and options in your browser. You may not be able to access some parts of this site if you choose to disable the cookie acceptance in your browser, particularly the secure parts of the website.   
We therefore recommend you enable cookie acceptance to benefit from all the services on the website.

### What are your rights

You may direct us not to disclose non-public personal information to certain non-affiliated third parties. To opt out of sharing non-public personal information with non-affiliated third parties, please contact a client service representative. An opt out selection made by one account owner of a joint account is applicable to all account owners of the joint account. An opt-out election must be made for each separate account you hold with us.

#### Communications

Unless otherwise indicated for a particular service, any communications or material of any kind that you e-mail or otherwise transmit through the services, including information, data, questions, comments or suggestions will be treated as non-proprietary and non-confidential. By accepting this agreement you grant a license to us to use your communications in any way we think fit, either on the website or elsewhere, with no liability or obligation to you. We are free to use any idea, concept, know-how, technique or information contained in your communications for any purpose including, but not limited to, developing and marketing products.

#### We are entitled, but not obligated, to review or retain your Communications.

We may monitor your communications to evaluate the quality of service you receive. Your compliance with this agreement is paramount to the security of the website. You agree that monitoring activities will not entitle you or cause you to take any legal action in respect to the manner in which we monitor your communications. In any event we won't be liable for any costs, damages, expenses or any other liabilities incurred by you as a result of our monitoring activity.

#### Amendments to policy

From time to time, we may update this privacy statement. In the event that we materially change this privacy statement, the revised statement will promptly be posted on the website and we will post a notice on our website informing you of such changes. You agree to accept the posting of a revised privacy statement electronically on the website as an actual notice to you. 

Any dispute over our privacy statement is subject to this notice and our customer agreement. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. If you have any questions that this statement does not address, please contact a client services representative.

Third Party Technology

NetoTrade makes use of third party technology to collect information required for traffic measurement, research, and analytics. Use of third party technology entails data collection. We therefore would like to inform clients that NetoTrade enables third parties to place or read cookies located on the browsers of users entering the NetoTrade domain. Said third parties may also use web beacons to collect information through advertising located on the NetoTrade web site. Please note that you may change your browser settings to refuse or disable Local Shared Objects and similar technologies; however, by doing so you may be disabling some of the functionality of NetoTrade services.

#### How to contact us

If you have any questions regarding this policy, wish to access or change your information or have a complaint, please contact us via live chat, email or through one of our management centres with your concerns at:

Support@netotrade.com
